(Sincro: wyxchari)
The Macra Terror
Macra 惊魂
(第三集)
Keep away. Don't touch me.
离远点, 别碰我
- I'll obey.
- What's that? What's happening!
- 我会服从的  - 那是什么? 发生什么事了?
Doctor, that was it - that thing
in the picture! The Claw!
博士, 就是那个 - 图片里面的那个东西! 那个大钳子
They're in control.
是它们在控制我们
Take them out of here.
They're condemned to the pits.
把他们带离这里! 他们被判去矿坑!
Come on. Get out, all of you.
Out! Get out!
快点, 出去, 你们所有人. 出去! 都出去!
Stand by work shift. Stand by in the pits.
工作班次请准备, 在矿坑里准备好
Work shift standing by.
工作班次待命
The strangers are being sent
to you for pit labour.
这些异乡人被派到你这里来采矿劳动
Put them in the Danger Gang.
把他们安排进危险组
Your orders are correct, Pilot.
你的命令是正确的, 领航员
The strangers must be sent to
explore the new gas reserves.
这些异乡人必须被派去探索新的瓦斯储备
They are dangerous people.
They must be disciplined.
他们是危险人物, 必须接受纪律约束
Yes, Control.
是, 管理员
You will forget all that happened.
你会忘记所有已发生的事情
Yes, Control.
是, 管理员
The Colony enjoys hard work and happiness.
殖民地享受辛勤工作和幸福
We will not tolerate
the evil of such strangers.
我们不会容忍这些异乡人的邪恶
Yes, Control.
是, 管理员
You must serve the Colony.
你必须为殖民地服务
Keep watch on your friends,
一直盯着你的朋友们
and if you see anything suspicious,
report to me immediately.
如果你发现任何可疑, 立即向我报告
Yes, Pilot.
是, 领航员
# We are all happy to work.
我们都幸福地工作. 我们都幸福地工作
- # For the good of the Colony
- Ooh! Ooh!
- 为了殖民地更美好  - 喔! 喔!
What's the matter?
什么情况?
Dreadful. Did you hear that rhyme?
好吓人. 你听到那个调子了吗?
The man who wrote that ought to be
sent to the Danger Gang - not us.
写那个的人应该被送到危险组 - 而不是我们
- Ha, ha, ha.
- All right. That's enough.
- 哈哈哈  - 好啦. 到此为止
Ah, are these the three strangers?
啊, 这就是那三个异乡人?
Yes.
是的
Yes, you might call us that.
是的, 你可以这么称呼我们
They've been allocated 176 shift.
他们被分配到了 176 班次
Oh, very good, Ola. I'll...
I'll recall the shift leader.
哦, 很好, Ola, 我去...我把班次队长叫回来
What an extremely remarkable place.
What efficiency.
一个多么了不起的地方啊, 多么高效
What ever do you make?
你们制造些什么?
Silence.
安静
I thought this was a mine.
You know, where you dig up coal?
我觉得这是一个矿, 你知道, 就是你挖煤的地方
Ah, yes. But here, you see,
the rock foundation is a type of salt.
啊, 是的. 不过在这里, 岩基是一种盐
Now, at depths it generates gases
over the years,
现在, 它的深处长年会产生瓦斯
and these gases are extremely valuable.
这些瓦斯极其有价值
Don't bother to explain to them.
Just get them to work.
别费劲跟他们解释了. 直接让他们去工作
Aye. Well, you don't send a lassie
and an old man down to dig.
是. 不过, 你不应该派一个姑娘和一个老人下去挖矿
Old? What do you mean old?
I'm not old, Jamie.
老? 你说＂老＂是什么意思? 我可不老, Jamie
You'll do as you're ordered.
你们得按命令行事
Here's the leader of their shift, sir.
这是他们这一班次的队长, 头儿
Very well. Report any irregularities to me.
很好, 有任何违规都向我报告
Medok. How did you get here?
Medok, 你怎么到这里来了?
Huh! They threw me out of the correction hospital.
哼! 他们把我扔出了矫治医院
Apparently I'm a hopeless case.
显然我已经无可救药了
But why did they send you here?
但他们为什么把你送到这里来?
The one remaining punishment they could think of...
这是他们所能想到的最后一种惩罚
- to work in the Danger Gang for life.
- For life?
- 终身在危险组里工作  - 终身?
Oh, don't worry. You don't survive long
in this atmosphere.
噢, 不用担心. 在这样的空气里你不会活多久的
It's the gas. It gets everywhere.
It creeps into your lungs.
是这些瓦斯, 到处都是. 它钻进你的肺里去
And when you're down there,
you're right in the thick of it.
你如果到那下面去, 你就到了它最浓密的地方
Come on, Medok. Take them to their work.
快点, Medok, 带他们去工作
What's the hurry?
着什么急?
You don't want me to call the guard, do you?
你不想让我叫警卫吧, 想吗?
All right. All right. We're going.
好吧, 好吧, 我们就走
But, we are entitled to
a supervisor on this shift.
但我们这一班次有权要求一名监察员
Ah, yes. That's true.
啊, 是的, 这倒是
Yes. Well, I'm leaving this man.
是的. 这样, 我把这个人留下
Hmm? Oh. Well, yes.
I suppose that's all right.
唔? 哦, 好吧, 行. 我觉得这样行
But, it's much safer up here.
Isn't it, Medok?
但, 这上面要安全得多, 是不是, Medok?
- It is.  - Ah, I see.
- 是的  - 啊, 我明白了
I'm perfectly capable of
working in the pit, thank you.
我完全可以在矿坑里面工作, 谢谢你
Polly can have the safe job.
Polly 来承担安全工作吧
Uh, no. You stay up here, Doctor.
I wouldn't know what to do.
啊, 不, 你待在上面. 我不知道该做些什么
Well, I'm not sure I understand
all this machinery myself.
而且, 我不确定自己能否搞懂这些机器什么的
Do you not think you might make
better use of the opportunity, Doctor?
你不觉得你也许能够更好地利用这次机会, 博士?
What do you mean? Oh, yes. Oh, yes.
你什么意思? 哦, 是的, 哦, 是的.
Yes. I'll be supervisor.
是的, 我来当监察员
What was all that?
那都是什么?
Nothing. Absolutely nothing.
没什么, 绝对没什么
Come on you two.
快点你俩
Oh, you're going to issue them
with masks, aren't you?
噢, 你会给他们派发面罩吧, 会吗?
You aren't taking them down there
without any protection?
你不会是不给任何防护措施就带他们下去吧?
Surely you could have seen to that?
想必你可以搞定那个?
Oh, ah, here. You'd better take this,
um... this checklist.
哦, 这里. 你最好带上这个..这个检查表
But I... I would have liked a mask.
但我...想要一个面罩
This really is remarkable. Most interesting.
这真的是了不起, 很有意思
Yes. I suppose with a little adjustment...
是的, 我想只要进行一点小的调整...
Hello, Ben. Don't go.
Come in. Don't be afraid.
你好, Ben. 别走. 进来啊, 不用害怕
I have nothing to be afraid of.
我没有什么可害怕的
No. Of course not.
没有, 当然没有
It wasn't your fault
you betrayed your friends.
你背叛了你的朋友并不是你的错
The voices tell me what to do.
那些声音告诉我该做什么
The voices may not be right, Ben.
那些声音说的未必是对的, Ben
I do what I am told.
我按告诉我的规则行事
Yes, I know.
That's why you're here, isn't it?
是的, 我知道. 那就是你来这里的原因, 对吧?
To spy on me.
为了监视我
What does Control want to know this time?
管理员这次想知道什么?
Won't you answer me?
你不答复我吗?
You know, Ben, this is very unlike you.
你知道吗, Ben, 这很不像你
I...I don't know what you mean.
It is my duty.
我...我不知道你什么意思. 这是我的职责
It's hard for you to struggle
against the voices, isn't it, Ben?
对你来说, 很难同那些声音抗争, 是不是, Ben?
I warn you, if you spy on the others,
watch out Jamie doesn't catch you.
我警告你, 如果你监视其他人, 小心别让 Jamie 抓到你
He's not so tolerant as I am.
他可不像我这么宽容
Hurry up. Put on your equipment.
快点, 戴上你们的装备
You shouldn't make lasses do the work of men.
你们不能让姑娘们来干男人的活
The Danger Gang will do as they are told.
安排危险组干什么就得干什么.
It's a punishment for their failure to cooperate.
这是对他们不肯合作的惩罚
We do all the dirty work.
We go where the gas is worst.
我们干所有的脏活. 我们去瓦斯最严重的地方
It's your own fault, Medok.
If you obeyed Control...
这是你自己的错, Medok. 如果你服从于管理员...
All right. All right. Forget it.
打住, 打住. 忘了吧
I prefer Control poisoning my lungs,
to their trying to poison my mind.
我更愿意管理员毒害我的肺, 而不是试图毒害我的思想
What's that?
那是什么?
It's a gas strike.
是瓦斯泄漏
Go on! Help with the cable there.
快啊! 帮忙拿一下那里的管子
Go on. Hurry up. That's the alarm.
This gas is lethal!
继续. 快点. 警报响了, 这种气体是致命的
What does he mean?
他什么意思?
He means they've struck so much gas,
they can't channel it off.
他意思时他们挖掘出很多瓦斯, 不能把它们输送走
When it reaches a certain density,
that alarm bell goes.
当达到一定浓度时, 警报就会响
Hurry up! Get that cable to the strike.
快点! 把管子拿到泄漏点
Come on. Quickly.
加油, 快点
Quickly. Come on. Pull there.
快点. 加油, 拉过去
Pull, all of you. Pull. Pull.
拉啊, 你们所有人. 拉, 拉
- Polly!  - Leave her.
- Polly!﻿   - 别管她
Get that cable to the strike.
把管子抬到泄漏点去
Get her away from here. Away.
带她离开这里, 离开
Jamie, the head of the cable. Got it? Right.
Jamie, 管子的那头. 拿住了, 好
Put your masks on. They're in your pocket.
戴上你的面罩, 它在你的口袋里
Right. Now, help me with this.
好了, 现在, 帮我弄一下这个.
Hold it. Hold it, Jamie.
托住, 拖住, Jamie.
Right. Right.
好, 好
What's it all for?
这有什么作用?
It's a poisonous gas which we mine,
from the bowels of this planet,
我们从这个星球里面挖掘的是一种有毒气体
which kills us if we breathe it.
如果我们吸进去, 会害死我们的
No one knows what it's used for.
没人知道它是用来做什么的
Yes.
对了
Now one must assume that
the relative connection is constant.
现在我必须得假设相对连接是恒定的
Now, let me see.
现在, 让我看看
Yes. I think that's right.
对了! 我觉得这样对了
I should give myself ten out of ten.
我应该给自己满分十分
Oh, you did give me a turn.
哦, 你吓了我一跳
Where did you find it?
你在那里找到的?
What?
什么?
The formula.
这个公式
In my head. You know.
从我的大脑里
Don't lie. That is a secret known
only to three people in the Colony.
别撒谎. 这是一项秘密, 这个殖民地只有三个人知道
And you're one of them?
而你是其中的一个?
Naturally. And you're not asking me to believe
当然. 你不是要我相信...
that in a few moments you have been
able to work out a formula
在顷刻之间你就能够推导出一个公式
which it has taken our
combined computers years to perfect?
而这个公式我们是耗费多台电脑数年时间才完善出来的
It does seem rather a tall order.
看起来的确是个高阶的
Yes, of course. I know what you've done.
是的, 当然了. 我知道你干了什么
You've broken into our secret files,
haven't you?
你偷看了我们的机密文件, 是吧?
I wouldn't know how to do that. Take a look.
我不知道怎么干那个. 你看看
Well, you must have seen the document.
That's the exact computation.
是了, 你肯定看过文档了, 这个计算过程是完全一样的
Really? Huh. In that case...
真的吗? 哈, 这样的话...
Do you really mean to say
that you worked that out by yourself?
你真的是想说, 你完全自己推导出来的?
Well, I did have a little assistance.
哦, 我的确靠了一点小小的协助
Yes, I thought so. Who was it?
是的, 我也觉得. 是谁?
Oh, no, no, no. Oh, no. No person. No.
噢, 不, 不. 噢, 不. 不是人. 不是
I simply mean that I took readings
from the various dials.
我只是说我从多个仪表盘上采集了数据
They appeared to be related,
它们看起来是有关联的.
so I worked out the principle
that controls them.
所以我推导出来了控制它们的原理
It was simple really.
Like doing a sum backwards.
其实很简单, 真的. 就像倒着求和一样
- Backwards?
- Yes. You know...
- 倒着?   - 是的. 你知道...
Given the answer, what's the question?
就是给定答案, 找出问题
Wipe it away. Get it off there
before anybody else sees it.
擦掉吧. 在其他人看到之前, 把它弄掉
Oh, well. If you insist.
噢, 好吧, 你非得坚持的话
Ho, ho. There now.
喔呵呵, 看看
If anyone follows that formula,
there'll be an almighty explosion
如果有人按这个公式走, 就能引发一场巨大的爆炸
x to the power of y is derivative 2 3's of 6!
y 的 x 次幂是导数的 2 3 得 6!
Get it off.
擦掉它
What are they doing?
他们在做什么?
We call that probing.
我们管这个叫做探测
You're not looking for more gas?
你不是在找寻更多的瓦斯吧?
Oh, yes. We never stop!
哦, 是的, 我们从未停止!
There's a door here. Where's it lead to?
这里有道门, 它通向哪里?
I've no idea. To my knowledge,
those doors were never opened.
我不知道. 据我的了解, 那些门从来没有打开过
Could be an old shaft.
可能是一个旧的竖井
Why would it need such a new door?
And so strong?
为什么它需要一道这么新的门? 还这么结实?
Hey, look out!
嘿, 小心!
Ah, you've made the connection?
啊, 你搞定连接了?
Of course. Otherwise you wouldn't be here.
当然, 否则你不会在这里
Now, be careful, Medok.
现在, 小心点, Medok
There are other places worse than
the Danger Gang, you know.
有些地方比危险组更严重, 你知道吧
This is a high pressure strike.
You are going to need a stronger screw than this.
这是一个高压泄漏点, 你需要一个比这更结实的螺杆
- Don't touch it.
- I know what I'm doing.
- 别碰它  - 我知道我在做什么
- He's fainted.  - Aye. He must have...
- 他晕倒了  - 是, 他肯定是..
What are you doing?
你在做什么
- What has happened to him?
- He's had a wee whiff of the gas.
- 他怎么了?   - 他吸进去了一小口瓦斯
Get him up. I'll look after him.
扶他起来, 我来照看他
Yeah. It's all right, mate. Hang on.
好, 应该没事了, 伙计. 坚持住
How long do you think Ben was watching us?
你觉得 Ben 监视我们多久了?
I don't know.
我不知道
Do you think he saw you take the keys?
你觉得他看到你拿走钥匙了吗?
- Well, if he did, we're in trouble.  - Yes.
- 啊, 如果他看到了, 我们就有麻烦了  - 是啊
It just means we'll have to make
use of them quick as we can.
这只意味着我们必须得尽快使用它们
But where, Jamie. And how?
但在哪儿用, Jamie, 怎么用?
Let's try that wee door first. Come on.
让我们先试试那道小门, 快来
Give me the word if anybody comes.
如果有谁来就吱一声
Right. Lookout, OK.
好, 小心. 好了
Hey, you two, give us a hand.
嘿, 你们俩, 帮我一把
Um, all right. I'd better go.
嗯, 好的. 我最好去一下
Just a minute Polly. This key's turning. Oh.
等一下 Polly, 钥匙在转了. 噢
Good luck.
祝你好运
Aye. It fits. Come on, Pol...
是, 钥匙对上了. 快来, Pol..
Come over here, everybody. Lend a hand.
到这里来, 所有人, 搭我一把
What's that?
那是什么?
It's impossible.
这不可能
Is it more gas?
还是瓦斯吗?
No. It's an escape.
不是. 是有人逃走
That bell means that
someone has escaped down here.
那个铃声说明有人从下面逃走了
- It's Jamie.
- Your friend? That door!
- 是 Jamie  - 你的朋友? 那个门?
I'm going with him.
我要跟他走
Hey wait! Don't leave me down here.
嘿等等! 别把我一个人扔在这下面
We couldn't have an alarm.
It's impossible.
我们不可能有警报响, 这是不可能的
Calling Pit Guard.
呼叫矿坑警卫
Close exits to all gas shafts.
关闭所有瓦斯竖井的出口
Stand by. A prisoner has escaped. Shoot on sight.
请待命. 一个囚徒逃走了. 看见就开枪
But, if no one can escape...
但是, 如果没有人能逃走...
My keys! My keys! They were on my tunic.
我的钥匙! 我的钥匙! 它们本来在我外衣上的
You must have dropped them.
你肯定弄丢它们了
Special guards to cover
all exits to the old shaft.
特别警卫去把守旧竖井的所有出口
With Pilot's permission,
they may have to go on forbidden ground.
有领航员的许可, 他们可以进入禁地
Jamie? Jamie? Jamie? Ah!
Jamie? Jamie? Jamie? 啊!
Hello? Who's there?
哈罗? 谁在哪儿?
No permission is granted for the guard
to go on forbidden ground.
警卫没有获得进入禁地的权限
Repeat, no permission.
重复, 没有权限
They are not to cover the exit to the old shaft.
他们不得去把守旧竖井的出口
This is in use at this moment by Control.
当前它正在被管理员使用
No one is to go in or near the old shaft.
任何人不可进入或者靠近旧竖井.
Top priority.
最高优先级
They seem very emphatic about that.
他们似乎特别强调了那个
Control knows best.
管理员清楚怎样最好
But what if your prisoner escapes that way?
但是如果你的犯人往那边逃跑了呢?
- What will happen to you?
- I shall be punished.
- 你会怎么样?   - 我会被惩罚
Well, aren't you going to do
something about it?
那, 你不打算对此做点什么吗?
Control knows best.
管理员清楚怎样最好
Who has escaped anyway?
究竟是谁逃跑了?
We shall soon find out.
我们很快就能搞明白
It is Jamie.
是 Jamie
How do you know that, Ben?
你怎么知道的, Ben?
I saw him take the keys.
我看见他拿走了钥匙
And you didn't report it?
而你当时没有报告?
No.
没有
Why not?
为什么没有?
I don't know. I don't seem to
be able to think straight.
我不知道. 我似乎不能清晰地思考
Ben, you're recovering.
Ben, 你开始恢复了.
I always thought you were
a tough customer. Well done!
我一直都觉得你是一个硬汉. 做得好
Control knows best.
管理员清楚怎样最好
You don't seem very sure.
你似乎并不是太确信
Jamie took those keys. I must report him!
Jamie 拿走了钥匙, 我必须举报他!
Doctor, you know what's happened?
博士, 你知道发生了什么吗?
Yes. Jamie's got free.
知道, Jamie 逃走了
By my calculations
he's got a very good chance.
根据我的计算, 他有很大的机会
- Hold that for me, will you?
- What do you mean?
- 帮我拿着这个, 好吗?    - 你什么意思?
Well, as I understand it,
Jamie's in the old shaft.
哦, 根据我的理解, Jamie 在旧的竖井里
Yes. That's right.
是, 说对了
And for reasons of their own,
Control don't want anyone there.
而根据他们自己的一些理由, 管理员不想让任何人进去
It's forbidden territory.
那是个禁区
- So you think he'll be all right?
- I don't know.
- 所以你觉得他会没事?  - 我不知道
I'll be able to tell you when I've
tested this to see how lethal it is.
等我测试一下这个看它有多致命, 我才能告诉你
But what's that got to do with Jamie?
但那个跟 Jamie 有什么关系?
On this planet it's got
a lot to do with everybody.
在这个星球上, 它跟每个人都有很大关系
There now. Yes.
现在看看. 是了
Oh, Doctor. What on earth are you doing?
噢, 博士, 你到底在干什么?
I'm trying to analyse this gas,
and I'm not having very much luck.
我试图在分析这些瓦斯, 但并运气并不是太好
Is that the same stuff that we've
been pumping out of the pits?
是跟我们从矿坑里抽出来的一样的东西吗?
Yes. And they go to great efforts to get it.
是的. 他们费很大劲去采集它.
The question is why?
问题是, 为什么?
Ssh! Somebody's coming.
嘘!  有人来了
Ooh! Mustn't find this.
噢! 不能发现这个
Oh, the Pilot's not here. Let me help you.
哦, 导航员不在这里. 让我来帮你吧
No.
不
Always lend a helping hand.
永远伸出援助之手.
A willing friend makes the task lighter.
一个乐于助人的朋友会让任务变得轻松
I'll wait for the Pilot.
If I'm going to tell anybody...
我要等领航员. 如果我打算告诉任何人...
You are, aren't you?
你会的, 对吗?
I don't know what I'm going to do.
我不知道我应该做什么
I got these voices in my head.
我脑袋里面有这些声音
Sometimes I just think
I'm having a bad dream.
有时我觉得我正在做恶梦
But the voices are here to help us.
They are our friends.
但那些声音是来帮助我们的, 它们是我们的朋友
That's it. What about my friends?
对了, 我的朋友们怎么样了
I'll see you are reported for this.
If this were not an emergency...
fixme 如果这不是紧急情况
The bell stopped. Why has it stopped?
警报停掉了. 为什么停掉了
Because, young lady, the emergency is over.
因为, 年轻的女士, 紧急状况已经结束了
Does that mean he's been caught?
那就是说他被抓住了
It means they're closing in on him.
这意味着他们正在向他逼近
Thank you. But, why didn't you tell this to Officia?
谢谢你. 但是, 为什么你不把这个告诉官方?
You told me to report back to you.
你告诉我报告给你的
I see. Very well.
我明白了, 很好
The stranger who has escaped is
in the old shaft.
逃跑的异乡人在旧竖井里
Control will now give instructions.
管理员现在会给出指示的
All guards will leave the area of the old shaft.
所有警卫得离开旧竖井区域
No one must go near it,
even in search of the stranger.
无人可以靠近它, 即使是为了搜寻异乡人
Do not approach its exit or entrance.
Do not go in.
不要靠近它的出口或者入口, 不要进入
Officials are to stand by at the gas centre.
官员们到瓦斯中心待命
We will obey, Control.
我们服从, 管理员
Gas centre standing by.
What transfers do you wish made?
瓦斯中心准备好了. 你期望传输什么?
Prepare for gas to be diverted into the old shaft.
准备将瓦斯引流到旧竖井中
Inspect connection immediately and report back.
立即检查连接并回报结果
The old shaft. Doctor, that's where Jamie is!
旧竖井. 博士, 那是 Jamie 所在的地方!
They're going to pour this gas
in the old shaft
他们打算将瓦斯灌入旧竖井去
- gas they value above all else.
他们可把这些瓦斯看得比什么都珍贵
What do you make of that, Polly?
你有什么结论, Polly?
For goodness sake, Doctor.
What are you going on about?
老天啊, 博士, 你这是要干什么?
Don't you see? Control are not pouring this poisonous
gas into the old shaft to kill Jamie.
你没明白吗? 管理员并不是要把有毒瓦斯灌入竖井去毒死 Jamie
They've quite another reason.
他们肯定有其它原因
Doctor, you've got to do something to help him.
博士, 你得做点什么帮助他
Before we act, we must think.
我们行动之前, 必须先思考
Now, the Macra that have come to
the surface of this planet
现在, Macra 已经跑到这个星球的表面了
have not found sufficient gas in the atmosphere,
它们在大气中没有找到足够的瓦斯
so they've had to get somebody to
pump it up from down below.
于是它们不得不让人把它从下面抽上来
But, if it's life and death to them,
why do they waste it?
但是, 如果这瓦斯对它们性命攸关, 它们为什么要浪费掉它?
- Why divert it into the old shaft?
- That's obvious, Polly. Obvious.
- 为什么把它引流到旧竖井里去?   - 这很显然, Polly, 显然
Because there's something trapped
down there they wish to keep alive!
因为那下面有某种东西它们想让它活着!
Officia reporting. All connections
have been tested.
官方报告, 所有连接已经测试过了,
They are all one hundred percent serviceable.
它们都是 100% 可用的
Transfer of all gases may now
be made to the old shaft.
现在可以将所有瓦斯传输进入旧竖井
Stand by for action.
准备开始行动
The Colony. The Colony is happy to obey.
殖民地. 殖民地乐于服从
The Colony is happy to obey.
殖民地乐于服从
We've got to help him.
我们得帮助他
I'm doing my best, Polly.
I'm thinking at top speed.
我在尽最大努力, Polly. 正在用最高速度思考
There's a pattern involved here
- a combination of pipes.
这里有某种规律 - 管道的组合.
If one were to follow this one...
如果有人顺着这个...
Stand by gas Officia.
瓦斯官员待命.
All flow is to be channelled
through systems seven and eleven.
所有气体导向第７号和第11号系统
Seven and eleven. Now which are they?
7 号和 11号. 都是哪个?
All channels are ready.
所有管道已经就绪
Prepare to turn on at half blast.
准备打开到一半压力
All ready.
都就绪了
Now!
开动!
Seven and eleven. If that's the system in use,
7 号和 11号. 如果那是在用的系统...
it must go from here round up to there.
它肯定是从这里绕上去到那里
Officia is to increase pressure.
官方准备加大压力
Doctor, quickly.
博士, 快!
Polly, I think I've found the gas flow.
Polly, 我想我已经找到了瓦斯流向
The pressure's being increased.
压力正在增加
Turn on full pressure now.
现在压力全开
Full pressure in action!
已经开到最大压力!